How do you treat
Как вы относитесь к
Zadornov with exceptionalism
Задорнову с исключительной
and I respect him very much
а я его очень
Hello Wow, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Ух ты я из города
Khmelnitsky Where am I from and I see that you’re
Хмельницкий Вы откуда я да я вижу что ты
Khmelnitsky in general And where are you from? From the city of
Хмельницкий вообще А вы откуда Из города
hero Nuremberg are you some kind of music teacher
героя нюрберг вы какой-то учитель музыки
or
или
Collector No, I’m a programmer, I get it, it’s
Коллекционер Нет я же программист понял
cool  programs on bows,
прикольно програми на там Луках
crossbows, balalaikas, I program on everything
арбалетах балалайках Я на всм
that shoots and doesn’t shoot,
программирую Что стреляет и не стреляет
drinks and doesn’t drink, kills and doesn’t kill, you
пьёт и не пьёт убивает и не убивает
can show me a quiver with arrows, I’m
можете колчан со стрелами показать мне
interested, I’ll show you one arrow, but all the
интересно я одну стрелу покажу А все
others are just a quiver. I want to
остальные таки именно колчан Я хочу
see the quiver, not the arrow, but the
колчан посмотреть не стрелу а
quiver, it’s modern.  modern No,
колчан это современны современ Нет
there's no
это там нет
skin there Well, show me Well, that's what
кожи Ну так покажи Ну вот мне что
was interesting to me, yes
интересно было да бля Да что такое
[ __ ] Yes, what is it anyway? Yeah, what era I'm saying what era I can't hear you, but now I can hear you, yes, what era? Yes, what era in general, well, a remake, a
Да какая эпоха вообще ну новодел да же
remake, I'm saying that  modern Well,
новодел я же говорю это современный Ну
of course I did, did I understand what the hell are you
конечно я а я что понял что ли блин вы
saying, no, I thought it was
говорите там нет я думал это блин
some kind of historical, it’s some kind of
какой-то исторический это какой-то
modern, just bye [ __ ] You
современна просто поку бляд Ты что
didn’t think at all, you’re a Collector No,
вообще не думал вы Коллекционер Да нет
well, you’re in Nuremberg where you
ну а вы в нюрберг откуда
came from and came to work  I didn’t ask, I
попали приехал на работу я же не спросил
had to go to Chika I asked where they
должен был поехать в чика Спросил откуда
came from from a city in Russia from
Откуда попали из города в России из
which you can’t leave
которого нельзя уехать
What city is it, some kind of closed that you’re
Какой это город какой-то закрытый что ты
like in general I just don’t know
как будто вообще я просто не знаю Из
What city in Russia you can’t leave from
какого города в России нельзя уехать
there is one city in Russia from  which you
есть один город в России из которого
can’t leave It’s called Omsk Omsk And
нельзя уехать Называется он Омск Омск А
why can’t you leave
почему из него нельзя уехать потому что
it because it’s considered So you can’t leave it
считается Так что из него нельзя уехать
How is it that there’s some kind of anomaly Yes
А как это там что типа Аномалия какая-то
there’s an anomaly because no one
Да там Аномалия потому что никто не
can get out of there Why doesn’t it let you out or the
может оттуда А почему не выпускает или
minibuses don’t run Well  today, for example,
маршрутки не ходят Ну сегодня например
today they are making the T-80 there they are making
сегодня там делают т-80 там делают
pinocchio sunshine Well, what difference does it
буратина солнцепёк Ну так какая разница
make what to do there You can leave
что там делать Ти ж можно выезжать
from there well, you could always leave
оттуда хорошо всегда было можно выезжать
just you know such a blogger Varlamov
просто знаешь такого блогера Варламова
I know yes chickens and curly hair and he suddenly wanted
знаю да кур да кучерява да и он захотел
to become a
стать
governor a governor there so he  I
вдруг губером губером там так он туда
arrived there And came up with the idea that you can’t leave from there
приехал И придумал что оттуда нельзя
And I understood everything This is your local
уехать А всё понял Это его ваш локальный
joke By the way, your name is Andriy,
Прикол У меня кстати Андрий зовут вас
my name is Dimon-16 I
как меня зовут димон-16
understand And it turns out that you work for some
понял А вы получается на какую-то
foreign company as a
иностранную компанию работаете
programmer I work
программистом Я работаю
for until now I worked
на до сих пор я работал
for the government
на правительство
And now all the Russian-speaking,
А теперь всех русскоязычных
Ukrainian-
украиноязычный
speaking, Iranian-speaking and all of us were given a new name
ираноязычные и всех у нас всех повы дали
Well, like, you didn’t work for the government
Ну типа что вы на правительство не
Now we can’t work,
работали Теперь мы не можем на работать
so
вот
apparently In this regard, today it
и видимо В связи с этим сегодня
started burning, I realized this is such an office,
запылала дил понял это такая контора ко
Well, who are you working for?  now
Ну так А на кого на кого вы сейчас
you work I work for my own office
работаете Я работаю на свою контору
that is selling me further Well, like no, I
которая меня продают дальше Ну типа не я
don’t understand this Russian office
не понимаю такая Российская контора
German
немецкая
American I am a German office German not
американская я немец контора немецкая не
an office French
контора французская
belongs to French Jews what kind of
принадлежит к французским евреям что это
office is this that belongs to
контора которая принадлежит в Германии
French Jews in Germany This is because all
французским евреям Это потому что все
the offices are in Germany  belong to
конторы в Германии принадлежат
French Jews Cool Well, what is the
французским евреям Прикольно Ну а как
name of your office, is it some kind of
ваша контора называется это какая-то
Company I can tell if I say you
Компани могу сказать если я скажу ты
will show it somewhere that I will be shown later
где-то это покажешь что меня потом
Zavra I’m just interested I’m a Yarata
Завра мне просто интересно я сам
programmer they
программист ярата
give our body shop as if you remember yes
дают наш бодишоп как бы помнишь да
That’s how I am Johannes
Такой я Йоханнес
Pereira a black dealer  but no, so
перейра торговец чёрным а нет Так
wait, look, you are a citizen of which
подожди смотри то вы гражданин какой
country, I can’t
страны чтото не могу
understand something, the Federal Republic of Germany
понять Федеративной Республики Германии
And how
А как
long ago, 20 years ago, how did you get fired
давно 20 лет А как же вас тогда уволили
from your job? It’s just that no one fired you as a Russian speaker.
с работы Просто русскоязычной вы никто
So you said that
не уволил Так вы же сказали что с
my contract was terminated from a government job,
государственная работа мне прекратили
your contract was terminated  like
контракт вам прекратили контракт как
Who are you a citizen of Germany
Кому как вы же гражданин Германии
ae Yes
аэ Да
so to all citizens of
так всем гражданам
Germany who came from thirty-
Германии которые произошли из тридцати
one countries Yeah from thirty-one yes
одной страны Ага из тридцати одной да
who go Russia Ukraine understood Well
которые ходит Россия Украина понял Ну
why the former Soviet Union There and so
чего Советский Союз бывший Там и так
on Yes all everyone
дальше Да все все
including America
и в том числе Америка
so everyone now in
так всем сейчас в
In Germany, they stopped working
Германии прекратили рабочие
contracts for gomen like na
контракты на гомен типа на
yes, as you remember, this is the story Why no
да это как помнишь такуя история Почему
one wants to
никто не хочет
work like that, wait, look Why
работать так подожди смотри Почему никто
no one wants to work for the government in
не хочет работать на правительство в
Norway because no one wants to have a
Норвегии потому что никто не хочет иметь
ti
ти
Well, I don’t understand Norway
Ну не понял Норвегия
Well, okay, I don’t understand, explain to me what  -
Ну ладно я не понял объясните мне что-то
this is a 30-year-old joke Why
это этому 30 лет уже анекдоту Почему
no one wants to work in the
никто не хочет работать в правительстве
Norwegian government like this Because no one
Норвегии так Потому что никому не
wants to have a
хочется иметь
mail tweedled
mail траляля
dog Well, what’s wrong with the
собака Ну а что не так с
government Well, no one wants to
гове Ну ну никому не хочется
have a replacement of the first level gono not the
иметь замене первого уровня гоно не
first level but Well, what  funny
первый уровень но Ну в чём прикол хорошо
okay okay second level second gov
ладно второй уровень второй гов
Well you would like it when you are sitting with a girl
Ну ты бы хотел когда ты вот с девушкой
drinking and
сидишь бухаешь
she says to you like well let me
она тебе говорит типа ну давай я тебе
write to you may you write like Andreas
напишу мей ти ты пишешь типа Андреас
[ __ ]
[__]
l yes What's the joke Well there's a Norwegian sitting Well
л да А в чём прикол Ну сидит норвежец Ну
okay [ __ ] okay Well that's it  maybe it’s
ладно Бля ну ладно Ну это может быть
some kind of specific Yes, there’s
такой какой-то специфический Да не
something I can’t understand yet, well, well, well, the
что-то не могу понять ещё ну ну вчм ну
Norwegian is like that in Norway, all the
норвежца такой он в Норвегии се
work Okay, well, it’s like you’re not
работа Ладно хорошо Ты как будто не
Russian-speaking, I’m Ukrainian-speaking Yes, it
русскоязычный я украиноязычный Да
’s clear that there’s something I didn’t
понятно нуже есть что такое не
understand, okay Guy, don’t stop stop stop
понял ладно Пацан не стоп стоп стоп
Explain I might be joking I don’t understand Well
Объясните Я может шутку Не понял Ну
maybe I don’t understand what well how Imagine
может я не понимаю что ну как Представь
that your email is called with
что что твой email называется с
uh dog [ __ ]
ээ собака [__]
and Well just in all Soviet languages
и Ну просто во всех советских языках
[ __ ] is there a dog no Dmitry and
[__] - это там собака нет дмитри а
Dmitry You mean that something is
Дмитрий Вы имеете в виду что что-то
wrong  Well, for [ __ ] sake - it's laino laino in
на да ну на срали - это лайно лайно у
Ukrainian [ __ ] Holy [ __ ],
нас по-украински бля Ёб твою мать [__]
we live in this very different world,
мы-то живём то в другом этом самом мире
well, well, how would it be in Norwegian? Here's
ну как ну а по-норвежски как будет Вот
laino in Norwegian, it's somehow different
лайно по-норвежски оно как-то подругому
How do I know I  wasn’t there anymore Well,
Откуда я знаю Я там уже не был Ну так а
what’s the joke then the Norwegian will be shorter,
в чём шутка тогда норвежец короче будет
well, gono and now you understand yes That
ну гоно и вот вот ты понимаешь да Что
jokes There are
анекдоты Есть
highly specialized Russian
узкоспециализированные русско
specialized Well in this case
специализированные Ну в данном случае
Russian specialized Russian here Russian
русско специали русско вот русско
specialized yes for if you
специализированные да для если ты
actually understand these things about them  such
на самом деле этих вещей о них такая
[ __ ], just look And when Let me
фигня смотри просто А когда Дай дайте я
guess you How do you treat
угадаю вы Как вы относитесь к
Zadornov with exceptional
Задорнову с исключительной
I respect him very much I-in-in I immediately
Я его очень уважаю во-во-во Я сразу
understood Yes, I immediately understood that you have, well,
понял Да я сразу понял что у вас вот ну
his level of intelligence Yes, no, you didn’t
его уровень интеллекта Да нет ты не
understand, I’m with him  worked for quite a long
понял я с ним работал довольно долгое
time
время
and when he really earned money,
и он когда вот он реально денег
yeah, he gave a lot of his money to
угу он очень много денег своих отдавал в
historical
исторические
[music]
[музыка]
senile further Yes, now you
маразматик дальше Да вот вот ты
understand Yes What when now people
понимаешь Да Что когда вот сечас людей
say like this Yes you immediately People are
вот так вот говоришь Да ты сразу Люде
excited about us  dro That is, you immediately become
нас задорно дро То есть ты сразу станови
Well, it’s not people, but it’s fervently dro you
Ну так это ж не людей а задорно дро вы
for that is, you’re just turning into
за то есть ты просто переходишь в
someone into the
кого в
Nazis Yes, I’m turning Yes, look dude
нацистов Да перехожу Да смотри чувак
Okay, let me show the cards
Ладно давай я вскрою карты
Look, I have such a Nazi code,
Смотри у меня есть такой нацистский код
he looks at you like you’re a gov A  you know
он смотрит тебя как на гов А знаешь
why
почему
because you are the real Russian
потому что ты и есть реальная Российская
gov vulgar
гов
[ __ ] what an intellectual joke
говнище насколько интеллектуальная шутка
that's
вот
just people in
прям люди в
Norway But for them it's short for them
Норвегии Но для них это короче для них
it doesn't mean anything at all
это вообще ничего не значит пись на й
skarg or in your ban and a lot more
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
video I don’t show people sometimes I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need to write Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video schezh tsikava and korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational  link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini write
YouTube Слава украини пиши